Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, 1949-1996; Series II; 114.58; (100 boxes) + 12 broadside folders
  - Financial Records
    - Rockefeller Foundation correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 43)
    - Activities report, 1957-1958 (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous foundation applications, undated (Box 43)
    - Craft discussions, undated (Box 43)
    - First rehearsed reading of "Pop Goes the Weasel", 1957 (Box 43)
    - Plays seen (includes playbills), 1957-1958 (Box 43)
    - "The Limbo Kid" by Downing, Robert, 1957 (Box 43)
    - "Reap the Whirlwind" by Stovall, Miriam, undated (Box 43)
    - Press releases, 1956-1957 (Box 43)
    - Report of the executive director, 1957-1958 (Box 43)
    - First rehearsed reading of "Taffy", 1957 (Box 43)
    - Reheard reading of "Ride a Cock Horse", undated (Box 43)
    - First rehearsed reading of "A Psalm for Fat Tuesday", 1957 (Box 43)
    - New York Summer Shakespeare Festival, undated (Box 43)
    - Production observance reports, undated; 2 (Box 43)
    - Play circulation, undated (Box 43)
    - Financial correspondence, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Requests for nomination to Ford Foundation program for playwrights
      - Fellows, Hugh, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Haggerty, Bruce, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hasapes, Theodore, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Kramer, Muriel E., 1958 (Box 43)
      - Kitt, Henry S., 1958 (Box 43)
      - King, Roy, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Kelly, John Barry, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Keating, Aurel, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Katz, Robert, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Karlen, Stymean, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hubler, Richard, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hoopes, William (David Garney), 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hilliard, Robert L., 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hepburn, Dick, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hennefeld, Edmund B., 1958 (Box 43)
      - Heinberg, Paul, 1958 (Box 43)
      - Hect, Paul P., 1958 (Box 43)
    - Proposed plans, 1958-1959 (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Juan", 1958 (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Children", 1958 (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "God is a Clown", undated (Box 43)
    - Morgenthau correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 43)
    - Rockefeller Foundation correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 43)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 43)
    - Director observers, 1958-1959 (Box 43)
    - Rockefeller lecture project correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "The Towline", undated (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "The Ghost Children", undated; 2 (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Dance to the El", 1958 (Box 43)
    - First rehearsed reading of "Guitar", undated (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Oh, What a Beautiful City!", undated (Box 43)
    - Rehearsed readings of three one act plays, undated (Box 43)
    - Inge, William correspondence, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Production observance, 1958-1960 (Box 44)
    - Shanta transportation, 1957-1958 (Box 44)
    - Progress reports, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
    - Rockefeller lecture project, undated (Box 44)
    - Craft discussion, undated (Box 44)
    - Executive directors report, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
    - Egan, Jenny (Phoenix Theatre), 1959-1960 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "A Thousand Clowns", undated (Box 44)
    - Publicity, 1959 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Friday Dinner on Middle Neck Road", undated (Box 44)
    - Workshop scenes
      - "Houdini", 1959 (Box 44)
      - "The Kids", 1959 (Box 44)
      - "The Black Velvet Ribbon", 1959 (Box 44)
      - "The Middle of the Air", 1959 (Box 44)
      - "The Dirty Saint", 1959 (Box 44)
    - Petty Cash, 1959 (Box 44)
    - Contributions to New Dramatists services, 1959-1962 (Box 44)
    - Proposals, 1959-1960 (Box 44)
    - Rockefeller Foundation correspondence, 1959 (Box 44)
    - Bills paid, 1959-1960 (Box 44)
    - Todd, Dr. Harold J. correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
    - Finance contributions, 1958 (Box 44)
    - Production observer's report, undated (Box 44)
    - Report to the judging panel of plays not recommended, 1959 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "The Night Bridgid Mullaney Left Home", 1959 (Box 44)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1960 (Box 44)
    - Past director observers considered, 1958-1961 (Box 44)
    - Telegrams and letters sent for immediate fund, 1960 (Box 44)
    - Chairmanship acceptance letter, undated (Box 44)
    - American National Theatre Academy, 1960 (Box 44)
    - Celebrity tables, undated (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Crisis", 1961 (Box 44)
    - Forms - sample file, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed readings, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of 'Two by Four", 1961 (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Legend", 1961 (Box 44)
    - Plan for playwrights, undated (Box 44)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Nest of Echoes", 1961 (Box 44)
    - Plays produced and honors won, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Ground rules from panelists, undated (Box 44)
    - Script list, undated (Box 44)
    - Ford Foundation - director observer- Graham, Kenneth, 1960 (Box 44)
    - Tobin mailing, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Re-evaluation committee, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Observerships, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Ford Foundation - director observer
      - Goff, Lewin, 1960 (Box 44)
      - Foley, Lee, 1960 (Box 44)
      - Carrol, Vinnette, 1960 (Box 44)
      - Altman, Richard, 1960 (Box 44)
      - de Liagre, Mrs. Alfred, 1960 (Box 44)
    - Executive director's report, 1958-1961 (Box 44)
    - Insurance, 1955-1957 (Box 44)
    - Report on "Romulus" (James, Luther), undated (Box 44)
    - Reports, undated (Box 44)
    - Mottel, Syeus correspondence, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Schochen, Seyril correspondence, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Playwright observer- Stokes, Narda, undated (Box 44)
    - Workshop - theatre, 1961 (Box 44)
    - Studio rental - general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 44)
    - Mitchell, Loften - correspondence, undated (Box 45)
    - Playwright observers, undated (Box 45)
    - Lindsay, Howard - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Kelly, Nancy - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous files and correspondence, undated (Box 45)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts, 1961 (Box 45)
    - General correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Re-evaluation, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Thank you letters, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Samples, M. David - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous notes and files, undated (Box 45)
    - Ford Foundation - director observer - Wilson, Robert Nyde, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Ulmer, John - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Wishy, Joseph - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Sullivan, Roger - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Report of director- observer Wilson, Robert Hyde ("Mary, Mary"), 1961 (Box 45)
    - Director- observer program inquiries, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Donor lists, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Applicants for workshop directors, 1961-1962; 2 (Box 45)
    - Director requests, 1960-1961 (Box 45)
    - New York State Council on the Arts correspondence, 1965 (Box 45)
    - Newsletter, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Scene workshop "Tandem", 1961 (Box 45)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1961 October and November; 2 (Box 45)
    - Workshop productions, 1962-1965 (Box 45)
    - Panels, 1962-1963 (Box 45)
    - Panels- theatre professionals, 1962 (Box 45)
    - "Aun", 1962 (Box 45)
    - Workshop expenses, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Workshop programs and company, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Workshop plays
      - "He'll Be Me" by Mamis, Justin, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "Richard Comes Wednesday" by Couder, Jo, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "Postlude and Snowangel" by Carlino, Lewis John, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "Teufelmann's Inn" by Sherry, John, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "Don Juan on West Fourth Street" by Goldsmith, Gloria, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "The Dispossessed" by Friedman, Joel J., 1962 (Box 45)
      - "The Emperor of Biloxi" by Sipherd, Ray, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "High Sign" by Carlino, Lewis John, 1962 (Box 45)
      - "The Phonograph" by Mitchell, Loften, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Workshop financial reports, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1962 January- June; 12 (Box 45)
    - Panels, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Nominations for the executive committee, undated (Box 45)
    - Thank you letters, 1962-1963 (Box 45)
    - Morrison, Jack - correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Morgan, David N. - correspondence, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Rockefeller Foundation report, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Budgets, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Copyright forms, undated (Box 45)
    - Planning committee minutes, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Sinclair, Michael - correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Junquera, Victor, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Wood, Audrey - correspondence, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Testimonial letters from New Dramatists, undated (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Lecture series correspondence, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Tape library (partial listing), undated (Box 45)
    - Bentley tape introduction, undated (Box 45)
    - Witt, Peter and ARA, undated (Box 45)
    - Craft discussions, 1962-1965 (Box 45)
    - Newsletter, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Press Agents, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Boettcher, Henry - correspondence, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Craft discussion (book), 1962 Fall (Box 45)
    - Space, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    - Rehearsed readings
      - "Look at my Man" by Lemay, Harding, 1963 (Box 45)
      - "A Young Man's Guide to the Upper Air" by Best, Charles, 1963 (Box 45)
      - "Once in Arcadia" and "Flower Pots on a Windowsill" by Parchman, William, 1963 (Box 45)
      - "The Apple Doesn't Fall" by Radano, Gene, 1963 (Box 45)
      - "The Ruins By Moonlight", 1963 (Box 45)
      - "Telemachus" by Carlino, Lewis John, 1963 (Box 45)
    - Panels, 1963-1967 (Box 45)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 45)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Wedding Band" and "The Wings of Time" by Alice Childress, 1963 (Box 45)
    - Acting classes - observers, 1963-1964 (Box 46)
    - Playwriting content, 1963 (Box 46)
    - Contributions, 1963 (Box 46)
    - General correspondence, 1963; 9 (Box 46)
    - Industry campaign, 1963 (Box 46)
    - Actors fund project, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Rehearsed readings
      - "The Gentle Art of Making Enemies" by Friedman, Joel, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "From a Dark Land" by Lemay, Harding, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "The Minotaur" by Scott, Joe, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Better Love Next Time" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Ride the Cock Horse" by Scott, Joe, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Viazemsky" by Terpiloff, Tony, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "A Cup of Elijah" by Mamis, Justin, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Nathan Weinstein's Daughter" by Rayfiel, David, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Does a Tiger Wear a Necktie?" by Petersen, Don, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "Q for Quasimodo" by Yablonsky, Harold, 1964 (Box 46)
      - "The Artists", "Spit in the Ocean", and "A Limb of Snow" by Barlow, Anna Marie, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous theatre notes, 1965-1966 (Box 46)
    - Observers, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Newsletters, 1964-1966 (Box 46)
    - Directors correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 46)
    - General correspondence, 1964; 12 (Box 46)
    - Rehearsed readings
      - "Husbands and Wives" by Pittman, Arthur, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "The Mute Who Sang" by Radano, Gene, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "A Week from Today" by Wexler, Norman, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "The Drapes Come" by Dizenzo, Charles, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Overture" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Better Love Next Time" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Home by Hollywood" by Hailey, Oliver, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "The Girl" by Welles, Violet, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "The Bed Was Full" by Drexler, Rosalyn, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Class in America" and "A Sacrament" by Pittman, Arthur, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Animal" and "The Picture" by Hailey, Oliver, 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Kissin' Rattlesnakes Can Be Fun" by Elder, Lonne, 1965 (Box 46)
    - General correspondence, 1965; 12 (Box 46)
    - Craft discussions - ideas, 1964-1965 (Box 47)
    - Stage manager notes, undated (Box 47)
    - Studio notes, undated (Box 47)
    - New York State Council on the Arts annual report, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Theatre notes, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
    - Craft discussions, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
    - Programs and companies, 1965-1967 (Box 47)
    - Rehearsed readings
      - "Cherry Soda Water" by Levi, Stephen, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "The Exiles" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "The Surprise Party" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Deadlock" by Radano, Gene, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "The Peace Creeps" by Wolfson, John, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Johnny No Trump" by Mercier, Mary, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Villon" by Parchman, William, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Seven Million Listeners Can't Be Wrong" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "The Investigation" and "Hot Buttered Roll" by Drexler, Rosalyn, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "I Ran into this Zulu" by Marmorstein, Malcolm, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Fat Rubinstein" by Foreman, Richard, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Nero" by Dizenzo, Charles, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Prunella and Blurr" by Max, Jerome, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Needmore" and "Needmore's Mother" by Parchman, Bill, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Apples and Innocence" by Mamis, Justin, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Mr. and Mrs. Lyman" by Friedman, Joel, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "The Little Birds Fly" by Lamay, Harding, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "Who's Happy Now" by Hailey, Oliver, 1966 (Box 47)
      - "What Color Goes with Brown" by Max, Jerry, 1966 (Box 47)
    - General correspondence, 1966; 12 (Box 47)
    - "The Caucasian Chalk Circle" by Brecht, Bertolt, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Leases, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
    - University of Michigan correspondence, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Photographers, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Playwrights, group theatres, etc., 1966 (Box 47)
    - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison, 1962-1966 (Box 47)
    - Executive committee meeting, 1962-1965 (Box 47)
    - Boston University correspondence, 1966 (Box 47)
    - WNET Channel 13 correspondence, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Production observers, 1962-1966 (Box 47)
    - General correspondence, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Directors lists and visits, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Assorted reviews, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Observerships, 1967 (Box 47)
    - General correspondence, 1967; 8 (Box 47)
    - Cash receipts, 1953-1967 (Box 47)
    - Observership appeal, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Theatre admissions, 1967-1968 (Box 47)
    - New playwrights catalogue volume III, undated (Box 47)
    - "Keep Tightly Closed in a Cool Dark Place" by Terry, Megan, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Workshop activities, 1969-1974 (Box 47)
    - Leases, 1963-1969 (Box 47)
    - Panels, 1968-1969 (Box 48)
    - Loessin, Ed - correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 48)
    - "Sister Sadie and the Sons of Sam" by Mason, Clifford, 1968 (Box 48)
    - General correspondence, 1968 July and April; 2 (Box 48)
    - Mason, Clifford - notes, 1968-1972 (Box 48)
    - Productions by New Dramatists for annual activities report, 1967-1968 (Box 48)
    - Arts of the Theatre Foundation correspondence, 1969-1980 (Box 48)
    - Workshops, 1968-1969 (Box 48)
    - Theatre admissions, 1968-1969 (Box 48)
    - Real estate taxes, 1969 (Box 48)
    - General correspondence, 1969 September-November; 4 (Box 48)
    - Proposals, 1951-1969 (Box 48)
    - New Dramatists Committee letter, 1969 (Box 48)
    - End of year mailing, 1969 (Box 48)
    - Script reading project, 1970 (Box 48)
    - Drama Guild quarterly piece, 1970 (Box 48)
    - New York State Council on the Arts grant, 1970 (Box 48)
    - Contributions of $100 and over made to the New Dramatists Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 48)
    - New Dramatists Committee, Inc. cash budget, 1970-1971 (Box 48)
    - Report to the judging panel of plays not recommended, undated (Box 48)
    - General correspondence, 1970 January-March; 3 (Box 48)
    - "Angels", 1971 (Box 48)
    - Tax information, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Progress reports, 1971 (Box 48)
    - General correspondence, 1971 July- August (Box 48)
    - Theatre admissions, 1972-1973 (Box 48)
    - Membership meeting, 1971 (Box 48)
    - Theatre admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 48)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 48)
    - Newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box 48)
    - Angel mailing, 1971 (Box 48)
    - Script reading project, 1971-1976 (Box 48)
    - Osborne, Betty, 1972 (Box 48)
    - Fund drive, 1972 (Box 48)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1972-1974 (Box 48)
    - Mini-benefit #1 "Beggar's Opera", 1972 (Box 48)
    - Jerome Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Box 48)
    - Progress report, 1972 (Box 48)
    - Benefit ticket sales, 1973 (Box 48)
    - Company Theatre Foundation, 1972 (Box 48)
    - National Theatre Institute, undated (Box 48)
    - General correspondence, 1972 June (Box 48)
    - Activities report, 1973-1974 (Box 48)
    - Benefit information, undated (Box 48)
    - Greenberg, Edward, 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Scrambled Eggs", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Elagabalus", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Hello, I Love You", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "The Family House", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Birth", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Rosensweig F. C.", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "All is Bright", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Babylon", 1973 (Box 49)
    - Program guidelines, 1973 (Box 49)
    - "I'd Go to Heaven if I Was Good", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Yucca Flats", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "The Partnership", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "American Glands", 1973 (Box 49)
    - "Nestless Bird", 1973 (Box 49)
    - General correspondence, 1973; 7 (Box 49)
    - Meeting notes, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Printed materials of New Dramatists, undated (Box 49)
    - Re-evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 49)
    - Contact sheets, 1974-1976 (Box 49)
    - "The Beach Children", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "200 Years of American Furniture", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "In the Dark" and "Soft Shoulders", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "Veil of Infamy", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "Trial of Denmark Vesey", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The War Party", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Rapists", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Rabinowitz Gambit", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Off-Season", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Salty Dog Saga", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Inn at Lydda", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "Love One Another", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Rag Doll", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "A Safe Place", 1974; 2 (Box 49)
    - "Leave of Absence", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "Give My Regards to Broadway", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Deadlock", 1974 (Box 49)
    - "The Shaft of Love", 1974; 2 (Box 49)
    - New York State Board of Social Welfare - notice of proposed rule making, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Membership lists, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Twenty-fifth anniversary celebration, 1974 April 26 (Box 49)
    - "Amoureuse", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Between Now and Then", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Nightlight", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Breadwinner", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Carnival Dreams", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Esther", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "Cakes with the Wine", 1975 (Box 49)
    - "The Pink Palace", 1975 (Box 49)
    - New Dramatists members (draft), 1950-1975 (Box 49)
    - "The Inn at Lydda", 1975 (Box 49)
    - Benefit luncheon, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Rules and regulations, undated (Box 49)
    - Newsletters, 1971 (Box 49)
    - Special evenings: friends and board, 1975 (Box 49)
    - Engler, Ms., 1975-1978 (Box 49)
    - Cash disbursements, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Billy Rose Theatre Books Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 49)
    - Broadway Show League, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Membership lists, 1952-1977 (Box 49)
    - National Endowment for the Arts grant, 1976-1977 (Box 49)
    - Renovations, undated (Box 49)
    - Newsletter, 1977 (Box 49)
    - "Firstborn" and "The Cold Wind and the Warm" production observance reports, undated (Box 49)
    - Financial records, undated; 6 (Box 50)
    - Ford Foundation account, undated (Box 50)
    - Lindsay & Crouse Studio, undated (Box 50)
    - Cash disbursement, 1976 May 31 (Box 50)
    - Artist reimbursement, 1983-1984 (Box 50)
    - Audit, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Service contracts, 1982-1984 (Box 50)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1982-1984 (Box 50)
    - Checks, undated; 3 (Box 50)
    - Petty cash, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Revised proposals, 1955-1956 (Box 51)
    - Bills paid, 1957 (Box 51)
    - Financial records, undated (Box 51)
    - Dunn, Tom - expenses, 1983 (Box 51)
    - Budget, 1962 (Box 51)
    - Receipts, checks, and deposit slips, undated; 3 (Box 51)
    - Prager, June - expenses, 1983 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Expense reports, 1982 (Box 51)
    - Artists fees (children), 1982-1983 (Box 51)
    - Panelists' honorariums (Prager), 1982 (Box 51)
    - Readers' fee (Prager), 1982 (Box 51)
    - New Dramatists Committee special account, 1954-1955 (Box 51)
    - Paid bills, 1969-1971; 3 (Box 51)
    - Publicity, 1969 (Box 52)
    - Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 52)
    - Report on fund raising campaign, 1971 (Box 52)
    - Weissberger memo, 1971 (Box 52)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
    - Financial statements, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1972-1974; 2 (Box 52)
    - Re-evaluation, 1973 (Box 52)
    - Composers, and lyricists, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Industry chairman Prince, Harold, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Rehearsed readings, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Theatre owners, undated (Box 52)
    - Critics, undated (Box 52)
    - Playwrights, undated (Box 52)
    - Summer theatres, undated (Box 52)
    - Directors and choreographers, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Benefit performance of "A Little Night Music", 1972 (Box 52)
    - Press agents, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Suppliers, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Accountants, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Producers, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Publishers, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Designers, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Regional theatres, 1972 (Box 52)
    - General correspondence, 1972 January and March; 2 (Box 52)
    - Request for assistance from New York State Council on the Arts, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
    - Financial records, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Script log, undated (Box 52)
    - Year-end letter, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Fund-raising records, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Cash disbursements, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Last foundations, undated (Box 52)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
    - Executive committee, undated (Box 52)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
    - Directors, 1978 (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous files, undated (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
    - Long-range plan meetings, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Admission letters: artistic directors, 1982 (Box 53)
    - O'Neill theatre contact list, undated (Box 53)
    - The Playwrights Center, undated (Box 53)
    - Press releases, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
    - Re-evaluation schedules, undated (Box 53)
    - Cast contact sheet, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Readings schedule and attendance, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
    - Artistic directors, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
    - Memory letters, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Computers, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Membership bulletins, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
    - Financial records, 1981-1982 (Box 53)
    - ScriptShare marketing: regional theatres, undated (Box 53)
    - Audits, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
    - Off Off Broadway Alliance labels, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Playbill award, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Proposal back-up, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Third stage, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
    - Programs for readings, undated (Box 53)
    - Admission letters: playwrights, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Backer's audition, undated (Box 53)
    - Admissions: records of finalists, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Archives, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Luncheon celebrities, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
    - Theatre Profiles volume 4, 1979 (Box 53)
    - Friends, 1979-1980; 2 (Box 53)
    - Cash disbursement journals, 1979 (Box 53)
    - Equity, undated (Box 53)
    - National Endowment for the Arts literature, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
    - Membership lists, 1979 (Box 53)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978-1979 (Box 53)
    - Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
    - Re-evaluations, 1978 (Box 53)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1978-1979 (Box 53)
    - Dave's stuff, undated (Box 54)
    - Children, undated (Box 54)
    - Long range plan, 1984 (Box 54)